Contact

8239994639 (Home) akhilkothi06@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/akhilkothi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

Microsoft Excel
Microsoft Office

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Professional Working)
Telugu (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Digital Marketing - Certificate of Training

Honors-Awards

Second Winner

Akhil Kothi

IIM Raipur 2020-22 | Transorg Analytics | NIT JAIPUR 2013-17 | Mumbai

Summary

35 months experienced Analyst with a demonstrated history of working with clients from Indian Telecommunications industry and one of the worlds renowned companies in hospitality industry. Skilled in SQL, Python, Microsoft Excel and POWER BI. Worked on projects which involved machine learning techniques like Logistic and Linear Regression, Data mining.

Experience

TransOrg Analytics 3 years 2 months

Analytics Specialist April 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 4 months) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Data Analyst June 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 10 months) Gurgaon, Haryana, India

Placement and training Cell, MNIT Jaipur Student Placement Coordinator June 2016 - May 2017 (1 year) Jaipur Area, India

Part of a 20 member team that works under the guidance of a Faculty Coordinator for the complete placements of MNIT Jaipur. My work was to approach companies with the proposal, convince them to come on campus for recruitment. The team worked for the session of 2016-17 and was responsible for the 500 placement offers of the batch.

Entrepreneurship Development Cell, MNIT Jaipur Student Coordinator January 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 5 months) Jaipur Area, India

I have lead the team of ED-CELL under the guidance of a Faculty Coordinator. The motto of cell is to create awareness about entrepreneurship among the students. The cell does it through a student team of 35-40 members who Works to organize various Entrepreneurial activities, Startup talks . Also the cell approaches various startups to provide incubation at MIIC - MNIT Innovation and Incubation center.

MNIT Mavericks Editor August 2014 - May 2015 (10 months) Jaipur

MNIT mavericks is a student media team of MNIT Jaipur. My work as an EDITOR was to prepare monthly news letters for college. To write news columns about achievements of people from MNIT. Also to cover news about various events, activities, workshops that are organised by various societies of the college.

Education

Indian Institute of Management Raipur

Post-Graduate Program in Managemnet (2020 - 2022)

Malaviya National Institute of Technology Jaipur Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Metallurgical and Materials Engineering · (2013 - 2017)

Narayana Junior College, Dilsukhnagar, Hyderabad. Higher Secondary School certificate, Science(Maths-Physics-Chemistry) · (2010 - 2012)

Naagarjuna High School, Hyderabad Secondary school certificate, High School Certificate of Competence Program · (2008 - 2010)